How does a product look like when it is given in the starting?
Suppose this is the sentence.
Now the entire market sits in one standardized view.
Now I have skipped this video and come down.
And I am watching the video, so I don't have to tell it.
That it sits in one view.
Okay, you can tell it.
But what is this?
You have to see it there only.
I can see the standardized view.
So let's put a plus button there.
No, there is no plus button.
There is no friction.
What you have to do is...
Oh no, why are you making it so complex?
In the background of the section, there will be...
There will be an Excel sheet.
It is light in the background.
And one standardized view.
I can see the view from the back.
But it has been shown from the top.
So it will be seen.
What is the problem?
And there is the same problem.
It can be cancelled.
Basically, I feel that the standardized view...
And I don't want to be scammed.
Their visuals are also there.
So should I put something there?
No, no.
No, there is no clicking.
The thing is, I have paid more attention to the wording.
I have paid more attention to the graphics.
I don't want to make graphics.
The wordings are made immediately.
No, no.
Actually, let's not talk about this section.
In this section, there is a unique point at the bottom.
Help towards what you need.
Guides that walk you through a home road.
So this point...
I relate this point to that point.
We bring everything to you.
You do it in front of you.
We don't ask for help from you.
This comes down to that.
Guides.
We make a guide.
Every bank's home loan in the same way.
This goes to the point of standardized view.
Browse before you give your number.
This is also the same as before.
One application is also covered.
And this is the same as before.
You can do it yourself.
You can ask us.
But you have to do it yourself.
I haven't said this for a while.
I think this is the seventh
unique point
that we want to convey.
So here we found
some supplementary
information that we
want to add on to the six unique points
covered before.
And we found a seventh unique point
that we want to convey to the customers
which is help
towards what you need.
So this sentence
what does it mean?
I wanted to say it because
I was feeling it.
It's nice.
It makes you dance.
This is also
the same as before.
The same as before.
And what is this video?
Yes.
It's a word that you can scrap.
Because these two
are in the lower section.
This is the first one.
The other one is the new one.
Okay.
Let's scrap this
section as well.
But it's scattered everywhere.
Sorry.
I don't know if you like it or not.
We can use this word
somewhere.
Maybe scattered information is
consolidated here.
Let's see
what kind of word it is.
Because
we don't want to get carried away.
We want to convey only one information.
Standardization, scatterization,
consolidation.
We are not writing an essay.
This section also
let's get rid of it.
This section also let's get rid of it.
Just pick important, this unique point
from here. And supplementary
information of other unique points from here.
And let's
refactor these four dark sections.
To convey
those seven unique points
in a
coherent manner.
With very few words, polished
English.
Such that points flow
into each other. And then
let's refactor into how those seven
points get distributed across
n number of sections.
This strip
is very big.
This strip is nice.
But I think
this padding above it,
padding below it is
causing some issues
over here. If it was
sticky to the
footer.
This footer
has a big heat strip.
If this padding section
itself was the strip.
And then everywhere
there is footer, there is this strip
on top of footer.
Basically, space is reduced.
It is the same for everyone.
Only space is reduced.
This was before.
But
there used to be holes in it.
Instead, it was stuck somewhere.
It used to be like this.
It needed some help.
It was stuck to the footer.
So we are talking about this
aside, site help
strip box.
Look at this. The margin
is 52.64.
Now it is 52.64.
This one is also there.
But that margin
needs to be fixed.
This
orange
orange, needs to be fixed.
It needs to be fixed to the footer.
This is the only thing.
This is for everyone.
It needs to be fixed to the footer.
The last section is in strip.
The strip is in the footer.
No padding will be there.
It feels like
it is a jumble.
One strip is there.
But this is not a section.
It is in strip.
But
this has some different place.
This is not part of the above sections.
It flows to the top.
Basically,
these two will fly away.
Then it should be put on the navel.
Navel has support.
It is just
for some help.
It is there for help.
But the thing is,
this section gets completed only after starting.
This section.
It is the same.
This does not need to be an independent section.
What is the current section?
You have to occupy the whole screen.
Then scroll
and go to the next section.
Then scroll and go to the next section.
And this is a mini section.
Then check the footer.
Yes, check the footer.
Okay, home page is done.
No, check the footer now.
Okay.
Then click the link.
No, no, just the footer UI.
Footer UI, no one cares.
It is not a disclaimer.
No one cares.
We have to show it at some different place.
If that is important to us.
So the footer is still the same information.
Yes, it is okay.
Everyone knows this is just
legal stuff.
Compliance.
No, from our perspective
does it fits or not?
It should not.
Yes, it does.